如果一个应用程序在后台更新
If an app updates in the background, but no one
但是没有人打开它发现它，那它真的发生了吗？
opens it to find out, did it really happen? Notification
通知开始作为一个方便的方式通知用户后台更新
started off as a convenient way to notify users of
但是它们已经成为一个强大的标准化的捷径
background updates. But they've grown to become a powerful standardized shortcut
来用更轻量级的操作方式直接和应用交互
to interact directly with apps in a light weight way.
从Jelly Bean（4.0）版本开始,通知可以被展开
Starting in Jelly Bean it was possible to expand notifications, making
让它们能容下更多的信息。
them larger and containing more information. That also introduced the
这就引入了富通知的概念，它可以包括这样的操作
concept of the rich notification, which is able to include actions
在通知栏的数据上直接执行操作
like these, to be performed on the data
这加速了交互
included within the notification. This speeds up interaction and
帮助用户简化他们的通知分类体验
helps users streamline their notification triage experience. As a
作为一个标准化的UI设计，在有限的屏幕空间
standardized UI designed specifically for conveying timely information in
输送及时的信息，通知机制的易用是明显的
limited screen space. Notifications were the obvious mechanism
当Android利用Android Wear扩展到可穿戴设备的时候
to use, when Android expanded in to wearables with
那些你为手机和平板电脑设计的丰富的通知
Android Wear. Suddenly those rich notifications that you designed
突然就对可穿戴设备兼容了,而且免费。
for phones and tablets make your app wearable compatible,
但是不要做得太过了，有用和垃圾之间仅有一线之隔
for free. Don't overdo it though, there's a fine line between
用户只用点击几下就可以
useful and spammy. And it's only a couple of clicks for a
永久禁用你的应用程序的通知
user to disable your app's notifications
所以看看下面的的笔记里
permanently. So check out the instruction
关于创建良好通知设计指南那部分的链接吧
that's below for links to the design guide in creating good notifications.